Ah, Sinon!
You're late, Kitty. Kirito.
Who's there?
I've been out here so long.
I might catch cold.
Sugo!
You did a very bad thing, Kirito.
You know, I can still feel the pain.
It's over, Sugo.
You better turn yourself in.
You're finished.
Finished?
Hardly.
There are lots of companies that
would kill to have me in my research.
And once it's complete there won't be
anything or anyone standing in my way,
then I'll be the god of this world.
Oh But first first I'm going to kill you.
Come on get up I said get up!
You think a piece of trash
like you can get in my way?
Did you think I'd let you slow me down?
Wanna know what the punishment is?
Death.
I won't accept anything less.
Damn.
My right eye's all foggy.
But I won't miss again, promise.
You bastard!
You little boy.
You're a piece of scum!
You don't have any real power!
And neither do you, Sugo.
I damn you!
No!
Such a weak weapon.
Too light.
No reach.
And it's all I'm gonna need
to kill you once and for all.
Oh, my God.
Hurry up, she's waiting for you.
Asuna.
Kirito. Asuna.
It's okay now.
It's over.
I fought the final boss just
now and the last battle's over.
It's all over.
I'm sorry but I can't
hear too well right now.
I think I know what you said though.
What you meant that it's really over?
And finally, finally, I get to meet you.
So anyway, I'm Asuna, Asuna Yuki.
And I'm finally back.
I'm Kazuto Kirigaya.
Welcome home, Asuna.
Thank you.
I can't wait to see the
feeling of the pain.
It's a true promise.
I'm telling you.
I'm not sure what I'm doing.
I'll just say that I'm not going to die.
I'm not going to die.
Oh.
Looking at this sentence,
Could anyone tell me how...
Looks like that's all for today.
Keep an eye out for
Homework Files 25 and 26.
And make sure to upload
your answers by next week.
Hey, can I come to you?
Thanks for waiting for me.
I'm tired.
Tired and hungry.
You're starting to sound
like an old man, Kirito.
Yeah, well, I feel like I've gotten
about five years older in the last month.
And by the way, it's
not Kirito, it's Kazuto.
This is real life.
You shouldn't call someone
by their avatar's name here.
Oh, sorry! I forgot!
Oh no, now what am I gonna do?
Everyone will know it's me!
That's what you get for using
your real name for your avatar.
Eh,
I guess it doesn't really matter because
everyone at our school is stuck in SAO,
same as us.
My cover's probably blown, too.
Asuna, are you getting around okay?
I mean, is the rehab you're doing helping?
I finally got the okay to walk
around without my crutches.
Although, the doctors say I
shouldn't run just yet. You will.
By the way, Kirito... What?
Do you know that everyone
in the cafeteria can see us?
Seriously, that little oversight
is going to cost you lunch.
Sorry, I didn't know.
Daddy!
I was wondering about your dad.
Is he okay? Mm-hmm.
He is, but he's still not
over this whole thing.
He quit as CEO and took
an early retirement.
And now that he's got all this free
time, he doesn't know what to do with it.
Hopefully dad can find a hobby
and maybe that'll cheer him up.
I hope so.
That night in the parking lot,
the police came and arrested Sugo.
Later when they interrogated him he denied
everything and tried to
pin the blame on Akihiko
Kayaba but after the police questioned one
of his employees Sugo
confessed to everything
As for those 300 SAO players
when they came to they
couldn't remember anything
about the experiments The good
thing is they didn't suffer
any neurological or psychiatric
after effects so everyone
can go back to their lives.
But the fate of virtual
Miss was a different story.
This latest incident practically
destroyed the industry altogether.
In the end, wrecked
progress was dismantled.
Its parent company also
suffered a big hit.
ALO was shut down.
No surprise there.
And as for the five or six other VR Miss,
with all the negative press
and the public outcry,
Their days were numbered, too.
You know who I was just thinking about?
The commander.
What happened to him?
Hmm? Oh.
Yeah.
Kayaba's dead.
They say it was suicide.
No way. Yeah,
when the world of SAO collapsed,
he did a high-output scan on his
brain and fried it when it was over.
So, wait.
Was he trying to copy his
consciousness to the net or something?
Well, it's one in a thousand shot for
it to work, but I know he pulled it off.
That day, Kayaba spoke to me.
Or his consciousness did anyway.
What's this?
The beginnings of a new world.
I call it the seed.
Once it sprouts, you'll know what it is.
What you do with it is up to you.
You can even delete it if you want.
However,
if you still have a tiny bit of
fondness left for the virtual world,
you'll take care of it.
Kirito? Kirito?
Don't forget, we're
meeting the others later.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, right.
Sorry, I was spacing out.
As always.
It doesn't matter whether
you're in the game or IRL.
The minute you relax, you
space out like a champ.
Seriously, Rika, you're driving
me crazy with all that slurping.
Leave me alone.
He's all over her and
it's driving me nuts.
Acting like that at school, it's so tacky.
Spying on them's kinda
tacky too, you know.
If I'd have known it
was gonna be like this,
I wouldn't have let you talk
me into a Montbonk truce.
I didn't talk you into
it, it was your idea!
You said we should let them have their
little romance for a month, remember?
I mean, God, talk about naive.
It's going to be cool meeting
everyone today, isn't it?
Yeah, I can't wait!
Sugu, I forgot to ask before.
Did you ever meet Egill?
Yeah, we went hunting together
a couple of times in ALO.
His avatar's ginormous!
Yeah, well get ready because
he's that big in real life too.
Prepare to have your mind blown.
Hold on a sec.
Were we supposed to get here earlier?
We gave you a later time to make
sure everyone else got here first.
It wouldn't be right for the guests of
honor to show up before all the guests.
Don't just stand there,
come on in. Uh, hey.
Okay, let's get this party started.
You all know what to do.
Ready, and...
Congratulations on beating SAO, Kittito!
Cheers!
Bartender, bourbon on the rocks.
Whoa, dude.
This is Long tea.
Thank you.
Slide me a big boy drink.
Klein, seriously?
Aren't you supposed to go back to work?
Alcohol makes the overtime go by faster.
Uh-oh.
Chick alert.
Long time no see. Hi, thinker.
How have you been?
I heard that you and
Yulia are married now.
I know it's late, but congrats.
Thank you.
But ever since we got back,
it's been taking everything
we've got to adjust to life here.
The good thing is, I'm
settling into work mode again.
Congratulations on getting that far.
Hey, I've been reading the
new MMO today. Nice job.
Yeah, I wish it were better.
It could have used a bit more content.
Oh, well, with the way Miss are now,
who needs walkthroughs and news?
Those things are going to
be irrelevant soon anyway.
You know what they say about
how the universe was born.
First there was chaos.
By the way, Egil, has
the seed been doing okay?
It's doing amazing.
We got 50 mirrors already set up.
It's been downloaded 100,000 times.
And check this out.
It's got 300 big-ass
servers actually running it.
After I visited Asuna at the hospital,
I took the thing Kayaba
called the seed over to Egil?
and asked him to check it out.
Turned out it was a full-dive
MMO that Kayaba developed.
It came in a program package
called the World Seed,
a stripped-down version of the Cardinal
system that could run on small servers.
Kayaba had modified the program so
that anyone with access to an ordinary
server could easily download it and use
it to create their very own online world.
After Egil said it was safe to use,
I had him upload it to servers across the
globe so that everyone
could access it for free.
It turned out that was exactly what virtual
Miss needed to keep the genre going.
As for Alfheim Online, all the data
was transferred to a new company?
that decided to keep
it online and running.
But the new Alfheim wasn't the
only world born out of the seed.
Everyone from individual
gamers to a few hundred small
companies were suddenly
creating brand new worlds?
on their very own virtual game servers.
The best part is they were
all connected to each other.
It's almost to the point where you
could create a character in one world,
then transfer it to another
with all its skills intact.
Hey, has anything changed
for tonight's after party?
Nope, we're still on for 11.
We're meeting up in Yggdrasil City.
I don't know.
You know, I had a feeling you
were going to fly too high up.
It's almost 11, so I came to get you.
Oh, okay, thanks.
Hey, Kazut, er, Kirito,
you know how ALO's got a
new company running it now,
and how you can use your
old SAO avatar if you want?
Everyone else is using their old
avatar, so how come you're not?
Hmm.
I guess because in that world,
that Kirito's mission is over now.
I guess so.
Then I was the first to
meet the Spriggan version
of Kirito and show him
the way to the world tree.
That's pretty cool.
Hey, Kirito!
Dance with me. Huh? Dance!
It's an advanced
technique I just mastered.
You just hover, then
slowly spin on your X-axis.
That's it!
Yeah, you're doing great!
MUSIC CONTINUES
Leafa? Leafa?
Anyway, I think I'm going to go home now.
But why?
Because...
It's too far away.
Like everything and
everyone else and even you.
I couldn't go that far even if I tried.
Sugu.
That's so not true.
You can go anywhere.
Anywhere that you want.
Ah!
It's coming.
Okay, what's up with the moon?
No way.
No way. Is that...
Isn't it awesome?
That's Aincrad.
The floating castle.
How?
I mean, what's it doing here?
I'm gonna beat it.
I'm gonna go floor by
floor, all hundred of them.
And this time, I'm gonna conquer it.
Leafa?
I went ahead and reset all my stats,
so I'm starting from scratch again.
Do you want to help me beat it?
I will.
I'll go anywhere. With you.
Hey, Kirito!
You're late, man!
We're going to leave you behind.
See you there.
Come on, hurry.
Come on, Kirito, Leafa. Let's go.
Hurry, Daddy.
Everyone's waiting.
Okay, let's go!
I'm not sure what I'm aware of.
I'm not aware of the wrong way.
I'm afraid of the back of my life.
I'm not sure what I'm aware of.
I can't see the sky in the sky
Here is a beautiful heart I can't see it
I can't see it in my dreams I can't
see it in my body
I can't see it in my
heart HIROGARI Test
KIZUKU YORAI WATASHI
Game GAIREBA Hero Sugou SUYOKU IRETE
NAKAI YUME MIRU COCOLO WAHTOSHI A-N-D-E-S
I WANNA ALWAYS TO BE TENTA
I'M GIVING EVERYTHING I HAVE
Thank you.